One more important thing to remember is quite tricky, and people are not talking about it a lot and
then talking here about your program in vocabulary, what they mean by that.
Actually, there are lots of words that you can use when you are talking about programming.
So person, understand you better word list correctly and you should not mix them.
And as a beginner, it might be really difficult for you because you don't know all this terms or you
are not really sure what you want to say, but you need to keep it in mind and try to improve with time.
For example, you must really understand what you are saying.
For example, I showed a function or I created a method inside my class, or this is an instance of
the class.
You must use all this terms correctly.
If you see a function but you are calling its method or maybe your column, it's something else.
This is not correct.
And then you will get lots of additional questions or you will be seen as a bad developer and you of
course, don't want that.
This is why you need to think a little bit what words you are using and try to use them correctly when
you are describing some program and stuff.