One more popular question that I'm hearing a lot is Blues write a function to check the palindrome because
actually this is what programmers are doing every single day.
They are checking palindromes, but whatever we can solve it.
So actually, if you don't know what palindrome is, this is a string which is the same from the beginning
and from the end.
For example, if you have full string, it's not a palindrome.
But if you have, for example, full of full string, it is a palindrome because it's the same string
from the start and from the end.
So let's ride this now.
And actually, it is really easy.
So what we want to do here, we want to create a function is palindrome.
And what we want to do, we want to solve it wisely and actually doesn't make any sense to split it
by letters and check every single letter and so on.
You can simply reverse a string and compare it.
This is why here we can write that our string equals and we can compare it with String Dot Split.
And here we just provide an empty string.
So we split it by letters.
Now we just make reverse.
So we're reversing our array and then we'd join in it again, which actually means better, worse this
world.
And we're comparing two same words.
In this case, we will get the same string if they are equal.
Let's check this out here where writing is palindrome and we are providing insightful and we're getting
false.
But if we will write full of fun, then we're getting through and the task is solved.