Another dumb task that you can get is at the link back to the source of the text after the paragraph
tech, and actually I have exactly the same issue Timberlake previously.
But at the end, we must provide a link to our source.
So how can we solve this?
First of all, we must create an Udham element, and in our case, it will be a link, then we will
provide insight.
And then we will just spend it at the end of our Dom.
So first of all, let's create a link for this.
We can use document to create element, and inside we must provide what Dom Element will want to create.
In our case, it is a name.
After this, we want inside link to assign our craft.
So we simply write Link Graph equals.
And in our case, I will copy it from here.
It will be asked for ipsum dot com.
And we also must provide insight and in a text, which will be a content of our link.
This is why Link Dot in the text and here were signing text generated from lorem ipsum.
So our dom element is ready now.
We simply need to put it at the end of our dom so we can write here Document Dot, Pointy Dot UPenn
child.
And here we just provide an Iron Dome element.
In this case, it will appear at the end of our body.
Let's check this out.
I am reloading the page, and now at the end, we have text generated from lorem ipsum and this is the
link and it is going on the correct page.