You successfully finished my course regarding preparing to JavaScript interview, and I think that you
are awesome if you finished it.
Together, we implemented 59 JavaScript interview questions and actually a lot of them were not easy.
If you didn't try it yourself, but just follow the loan.
You can still do that.
You can just randomly pick some video and try to implement it yourself, even if you saw it once, it
makes a lot of sense to try and do it.
Also, I just want to remind you to not be depressed if you failed the interview.
It will come with time and you will for sure, find your job.
You just need to gather more knowledge, understand what questions you have been asked in the interviews,
and prepare yourself better.
I hope that you learned a lot and they will see you in my next course.